http://www.messenger-inquirer.com/site/privacy.html

Sports
PRIVACY POLICYLast updated: March 8, 2019Paxton Media Group LLC (“Paxton Media,” “we,” or “us”) operates the Messenger-Inquirer website and any other services and pages that display or link to this notice (collectively, the “Site”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information when you use our Site. This Privacy Policy is part of and subject to our [Terms of Use and Subscription Agreement], which together govern Paxton Media’s relationship with you in relation to the Site. If you do not agree with any portion of this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Site.This Privacy Policy has been created in order to demonstrate and inform you of our firm commitment to privacy and to outline how we deal with any personal data you provide while visiting or using Sites or otherwise interacting with us via the Sites. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through the Site and not to information collected offline. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Paxton Media does not own or control, or to individuals whom Paxton Media does not employ or manage, including any of the third parties to which Paxton Media may disclose user information to the extent set forth in this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Use and Subscription Agreement.IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST NOT USE THE SITE OR DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION THROUGH THE SITE. I. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE A.                 Personal information CollectionWhile using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, phone number, postal address, credit card information, and other personal information. Sometimes this Personal Information is needed and collected when you register for participation in certain features of the Site, subscribe to our email communications, comment on blogs, or when you contact us.  Use of Personal InformationWe collect this information for the purpose of providing and administering the Site, subscription and account registration and maintenance, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and improving our services. In addition, we may from time to time contract with third parties to assist us in collecting, maintaining and managing our customer information, taking and fulfilling orders, processing credit card information, conducting promotions, communicating effectively with our customers, and providing analytics regarding your interactions with our Site and other third-party websites so that we may improve the products and services we offer you. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Paxton Media does not own or control, or to individuals whom Paxton Media does not employ or manage, including any of the third parties to which Paxton Media may disclose user information to the extent set forth in this Privacy Policy. Social Media PlatformsYou may also choose to provide Personal Information through social media platforms such as Facebook, Twitter, or Instagram (“Social Media Platforms”), when you communicate with us or other participants on the Social Media Platforms, post suggestions or comments for us, or enter a sweepstakes or contest through the Social Media Platforms. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not cover the privacy and security practices of the Social Media Platforms on which Paxton Media has pages, including without limitation Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn. Please carefully review the privacy policies and terms of service on such Social Media Platforms before using, visiting, or interacting with others on such Social Media Platforms. Please remember that any information you share on our pages or in general on Social Media Platforms becomes public information, and you should exercise caution when deciding whether to disclose your personal information in such a manner. In addition, when you interact with the Site through Social Media Platforms or third-party social media applications, sharing products or content through Social Media Platforms by sharing or liking such products or content, our third-party providers may combine information concerning such activities with other information about you such as your user name, gender, referring website, geographic location, and other information obtained through other third-party websites you visit as well as your public profile(s) on such Social Media Platforms. Such information will also become part of your profile or account as maintained by Paxton Media. B.                 Anonymous DataCollectionWe may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site or when you access the Site by or through a mobile device and that data that does not contain information that identifies an individual (“Anonymous Data”).This Anonymous Data may can include certain personally identifiable information that has been de-identified; that is, information that has been rendered anonymous. Anonymous Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. If you choose to access, visit, and/or use any of our pages on Social Media Platforms, we may receive aggregate information and analysis about visitors’ usage of our pages on such Social Media Platforms.When you access the Site by or through a mobile device, this Anonymous Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use and other statistics.In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Site's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.Please see the sections regarding Location Information and Cookies below regarding the use of your location information and your options.  Location InformationWe may use and store information about your location depending on the permissions you have set on your device. We use this information to provide features of our Site, to improve and customize our Site. You can enable or disable location services when you use our Site at any time, through your mobile device settings. CookiesAs is the case with many websites and web-based applications, the Site uses a technology called “cookies,” which are files with a small amount of data and may include an anonymous unique identifier. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet, and allows us to tailor your visits to the Site to your individual preferences. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The “Help” feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Site. Do Not TrackSome browsers have a “do not track” feature that lets you indicate that you do not wish to have your online activities tracked. These features are not yet uniform, so we do not currently respond to such features or signals. Therefore, if you select or turn on a “do not track” feature in your web browser or block or delete tracking cookies, Paxton Media and its third-party providers may continue collecting information about your online activities as described in this Privacy Policy. Use of Anonymous DataAnonymous Data is used internally for administration of the Site, troubleshooting, and to help improve the quality of Site and their design. We also use non-personally identifiable information to help analyze trends and statistics, protect the security and integrity of the Site, evaluate our online marketing campaigns, tailor our promotions or other offers to you, and provide location-based services. We may share such aggregated, non-personally identifiable information, such as demographics, with existing and prospective business partners and advertisers. We also may use cookies to collect product and purchase information over time from the pages you access or visit. This information may be combined with Personal Information from our records and other sources. Such information about your use of the Site will become part of your profile as maintained by Paxton Media. C.                 Behavioral RemarketingPaxton Media uses remarketing services to advertise on our Site and third party web sites to you after you visited our Site. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies and other Anonymous Data to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These targeted advertisements to you may appear on our Site or on other websites that you visit. Please click here to learn more about your choices regarding targeted and behavioral advertising: http://www.networkadvertising.org/ or http://www.aboutads.info/. To opt out, please click here http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. In all cases, however, we will only use your information as permitted by law.Without limiting the foregoing, we use Facebook for remarketing services.Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page:https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook:https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/#568137493302217Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/ or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook's Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation II. SERVICE PROVIDERSWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Site, to provide the Site on our behalf, to perform Site-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Site is used.  These third parties may access your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and subject to obligations that prohibit the disclosure or use of your information for any other purpose. III. COMMUNICATIONSWe may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us at any time by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send, or contacting us at the email address provided below, indicating that you no longer want to receive information relating to Site. IV. SECURITYThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you. Please do not use email or Social Media Platforms to communicate information to us that you consider confidential. V. SPECIAL NOTE TO INTERNATIONAL USERS.Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. If you are a user accessing the Site from a jurisdiction with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site, which is governed by Tennessee law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use and Subscription Agreement, you expressly consent to be governed by Tennessee law in order to use the Site and for the purposes outlined above. VI. SPECIAL NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTSUnder the California Civil Code, residents of the State of California that have provided any Personal Information to Paxton Media have the right to request a list of all third parties to which Paxton Media has disclosed Personal Information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if Paxton Media has a privacy policy that gives either an opt-out or opt-in choice for use of Personal Information by third parties (such as advertisers or affiliated companies) for marketing purposes, Paxton Media may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options free of charge. Paxton Media qualifies for the alternative option and has adopted a policy of not disclosing the personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option that prevents that information from being disclosed to third parties for those purposes. It has established this Privacy Policy that provides you with details on how you may either opt-out of the use of your Personal Information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, please send a request to csr@messenger-inquirer.com with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent. VII. LINKS TO OTHER SITESOur Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. Such websites are not investigated, monitored or checked for quality, accuracy or completeness by us. Inclusion of any linked website on the Site does not imply or express an approval or endorsement of the linked website by us, or of any of the content, opinions, products or services provided on these websites. We strongly advise you to review the privacy policy of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. VIII. CHILDREN'S PRIVACYProtecting the privacy of children is very important to us. The Children’s Online Privacy and Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”) defines a “Child” as anyone under the age of 13. Paxton Media strictly adheres to COPPA. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information obtained through the Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of the Site is structured to attract anyone under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. IX. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy is effective as of March 8, 2019 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Site after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, OR ANY SUBSEQUENT MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST NOT ACCESS OR USE THe SIE OR DISCLOSE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THROUGH THe Site. X. CONTACT USWe welcome your questions, comments and all feedback pertaining to your privacy or any other issue with regard to Site. You may contact us at csr@messenger-inquirer.com
46°
Clear
Out Of Work In America
New York Times Project
The past few months, The New York Times has coordinated a nationwide project to document the lives of Americans out of work. The study involved collaborating with 11 other local newsrooms around the U.S. The Messenger-Inquirer is the only newspaper from Kentucky in the collaboration. The resulting collection of stories was published Oct. 23, 2020, in the New York Times print edition and at nytimes.com/outofwork. The following list is the Messenger-Inquirer's recent local unemployment coverage; read more by clicking the "New York Times Project" header.
Owensboro only metro in nation with lower June unemployment
CVB expecting big things in 2021
State's fiscal outlook better than expected
Hancock one of nation's most industrialized counties
Pagan: New tax rates show city has 'weathered pandemic'
Police & Court Records
M-I police reports for Dec. 10, 2020
M-I police reports for Dec. 9, 2020
CommentedMcLean receives four food deliveries through USDA Farmers to Families, hopes for more (1)
Statue committee to make final recommendations  (1)
Our brains are too full these days (1)
Beshear restrictions are hardest on service industry, owners say (1)
State outlines initial plan to vaccinate health workers (1)
Beshear: Fighting COVID-19 has been 'hard emotionally' (1)
Election law at center stage as legal battles continue in several states (1)
Winterizing tools prepares for the next season (1)
Stivers says addressing governor's emergency powers essential (1)
Individuals are the key to fighting the virus, say judge-executives (1)
Utah senator blocks legislation to establish Latino and women's museums
Body camera footage shows police outside in raid of Rebekah Jones' home
© Copyright 2020, Owensboro Messenger-Inquirer, 1401 Frederica St. Owensboro, KY | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
